Neugass, Fritz; Papers ger007
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Published Writings by Fritz Neugass (clippings), 1942-1979; 10; 186 file folders
  - Photography, 1952; 19 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 37)
  - Photography, 1953; 23 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 38)
  - Photography, 1954; 14 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 39)
  - Photography, 1955; 25 items (Box 28 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 40)
  - Photography. Family of Man articles, 1955-1956; 25 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 1)
  - Photography, 1956; 6 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 2)
  - Photography, 1957; 20 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 3)
  - Photography, 1958; 13 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 4)
  - Photography, 1959; 8 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 5)
  - Photography, 1960; 10 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 6)
  - Photography, 1961; 16 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 7)
  - Photography, 1962; 7 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 8)
  - Photography, 1963; 11 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 9)
  - Photography, 1964; 14 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 10)
  - Photography, 1965-1966; 13 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 11)
  - Photography, 1967; 14 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 12)
  - Photography, 1968-1969; 15 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 13)
  - Photography, 1976-1979; 11 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 14)
  - General journalistic articles, 1953; 18 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 15)
  - General journalistic articles, 1954; 35 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 16)
  - General journalistic articles, 1955; 28 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 17)
  - General journalistic articles, 1956; 27 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 18)
  - General journalistic articles, 1957; 26 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 19)
  - General journalistic articles, 1958; 18 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 20)
  - General journalistic articles, 1959; 16 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 21)
  - General journalistic articles, 1960-1964; 19 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 22)
  - General journalistic articles, 1965-1976; 22 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 23)
  - Photojournalism, 1942-1947; 22 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 24)
  - Photojournalism, 1948; 19 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 25)
  - Photojournalism, 1949; 27 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 26)
  - Photojournalism, 1950; 26 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 27)
  - Photojournalism, 1951; 18 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 28)
  - Photojournalism, 1952; 23 items (Box 29 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 29)
  - Photojournalism, 1953; 30 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 1)
  - Photojournalism, 1954; 29 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 2)
  - Photojournalism, 1955; 33 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 3)
  - Photojournalism, 1956; 23 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 4)
  - Photojournalism, 1957; 13 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 5)
  - Photojournalism, 1958; 21 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 6)
  - Photojournalism, 1959; 15 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 7)
  - Photojournalism, 1960-1978; 40 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 8)
  - Das Kunstwerk. Issues with articles by Neugass (2), 1952; 1954-1955 (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 9)
  - Wereld. Issues with articles by Neugass (2), 1958; 1959 (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 10)
  - Freie Volksbühne (Köln). Issues with articles by Neugass (8), 1962-1965 (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 11)
  - Books and manuscripts, 1965-1967; 22 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 12)
  - Books and manuscripts, 1968-1970; 27 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 13)
  - Books and manuscripts, 1971-1973; 26 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 14)
  - Books and manuscripts, 1974-1978; 11 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 15)
  - Contributions by Neugass in the Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1964-1968; 125 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 16)
  - Contributions by Neugass in the Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1969-1979; 95 items (Box 30 (10-Published Writings by Fritz Neugass ), Folder 17)
- Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz Neugass, 1930s-1940; 11; 9 file folders
  This series contains early journalistic writings of Neugass, as well as an unpublished novel in German and accounts of his internment in the French containment camp of Gurs in 1939.
  - Geheimnis um die Venus. Roman von François Neuville. Novel by Neugass, written ca. 1939, published under a pseudonym in serial form in a Swiss newspaper, 1940 December-1941 February (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 18)
    Also printed proof copy. 64p.
  - "Une ombre passé". Nouvelle Inédite par ANDRE JAUGET, Undated; 7p (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 19)
    Typescript in French, presumably by Neugass, written under the pseudonym Andre Jauget.
  - "Chronik von Gurs", Undated (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 20)
    Typescript in German. 16p. Synopses. 6p., 2p.
  - "Tragedy at Gurs", Undated (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 21)
    Typescript in English. 20p. Also handwritten version, synopsis.
  - "Friends behind barbed wire". Partial typescript of a novel, experiences of Neugass and Louise Strauss-Ernst in wartime France. English, Undated; 124p (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 22)
  - Art reports from Paris. 3 typescripts, in German, Undated (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 23)
  - Articles on Neugass 3-month trip through Mediterranean countries, 1936 (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 24)
    Texts predominantly in German, also several in English and French. Typescripts.
  - Pre-US journalistic writings. Short texts, mostly 1-2 pages typed, in German, Undated (Box 30 (11-Early writings (pre-USA) of Fritz ), Folder 25-26)
- Documents and biographical materials, 1899-1979; 12; 12 file folders
  This series contains German documents, passports, documents concerning Neugass? naturalization as a U.S. citizen, as well as employment attempts during his early years in the U.S.
  - German documents, passports, 1899-1939 (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 1)
  - Last Will & Testament of Julius Isaak Neugass and Alice Sara Neugass (parents of Fritz Neugass), 1939 (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 2)
  - French documents, 1940-1941 (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 3)
  - Application for U.S. Visa, 1941 (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 4)
  - Applications for U.S. employment, 1940-1943 (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 5)
  - Certificate of U.S. naturalization, 1947; U.S. passports, Undated (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 6)
  - Vitae, publications lists, Undated (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 7)
  - Clippings about Neugass, Undated (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 8)
  - Clippings about photography prizes won by Neugass, Undated (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 9)
  - American National Red Cross memberships, Undated (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 10)
  - Memberships, press passes, Undated (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 11)
  - Account book, 1959-1979 (Box 31 (12-Documents and biographical ), Folder 12)
- Correspondence, 1941-1979; 13; 102 file folders
  Neugass? correspondence files contain a small amount of correspondence with German friends (1941-1948). Most of the correspondence dates from the 1950s-1979 and includes correspondence with publishers and artists such as Jimmy Ernst, Joachim Berthold, Buell Mullen, and Bernard & Ursula Schultze.
  - Early letters, 1941-1949 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 13)
  - Ehmann, Walter, 1948 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 14)
  - Kahn, Jula, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 15)
  - Liebreich, Lise, 1945-1948 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 16)
  - Moore, Fanny, 1942-1944 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 17)
  - Müller, Günther, 1948 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 18)
  - Picard, Ella, 1941-1948 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 19)
  - A - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 20)
  - Antiques & Art Monitor, 1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 21)
  - Arntz, Wilhelm, 1977; Clippings. (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 22)
  - Art, 1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 23)
  - Art News, 1972-1973 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 24)
  - B - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 25)
  - Bachert, Hildegard (re: death of Otto Kallir), 1978-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 26)
  - The Barnes Foundation, 1961 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 27)
  - Bavaria-Verlag, 1973-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 28)
  - Beardon, Romare, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 29)
  - Berthold, Joachim, 1963-1978 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 30)
  - Binder, Joseph, 1965; 1967 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 31)
  - The Boeing Company, 1962 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 32)
  - BolaffiArte, 1976-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 33)
  - Bruckmann München (Pantheon), 1974-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 34)
  - C - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 35)
  - Canaday, John (New York Times), 1963; 1966 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 36)
  - Castrvm Peregrini, 1966; 1976 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 37)
  - Christie, Manson & Woods International, Inc., 1977-1978 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 38)
  - D - E - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 39)
  - Demisch, Heinz, 1973; 1978; Reprints. (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 40)
  - du. Die Kunstzeitschrift, 1977-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 41)
  - Edgerton, Harold, 1956 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 42)
  - Emmer, Willi, 1959; 1970; Typescript. (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 43)
  - Eriksdun, Friedrich, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 44)
  - Ernst, Jimmy, 1961-1964 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 45)
  - F - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 46)
  - Finanz und Wirtschaft (Verlag), 1974-1975 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 47)
  - Frankfurter Allgemeine Zeitung, 1974-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 48)
  - Fr, Wolfgang, 1961-1978 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 49)
  - Frolow, Anatole, 1957-1967 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 50)
  - G - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 51)
  - H - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 52)
  - Halkin, Theodore, 1964 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 53)
  - Handelsblatt. Wirtschafts- und Finanzzeitung, 1970-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 54)
  - Harder, Wolfgang Baron von, 1949-1959 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 55)
  - Hory, Elmyr de, 1967; 1970 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 56)
  - Hug, Charles, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 57)
  - I - J - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 58)
  - Jacobi, Lotte, 1964; 1966 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 59)
  - K - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 60)
  - Ketterer, Roman Norbert, 1976-1978 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 61)
  - Kraus, H. P., 1959-1960 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 62)
  - Kraus, Ilse, 1969-1973 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 63)
  - Krause, Karl-Heinz, 1970-1975 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 64)
  - Kunst-Bulletin des Schweizerischen Kunstvereins, 1975-1978 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 65)
  - L - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 66)
  - Lehmbruck, Guido, 1972 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 67)
  - Loevenich, Karl, 1972-1973; Typescript. (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 68)
  - Losbichler, Ludwig, 1972-1973 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 69)
  - M - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 70)
  - Maeght Editeur, 1964 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 71)
  - Maier-Behrens, Ella, 1976 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 72)
  - Martin, Benita (geb. Von Harder), 1965-1967; 1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 73)
  - Martin Gordon Inc., 1977 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 74)
  - Merveldt, Hanns Hubertus Graf von, 1966 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Merveldt, Eka Gräfin von, 1969-1976 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 75)
  - Morgan, Barbara, 1964-1969 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 76)
  - Müller-Mehlis, Reinhard (Cleveland Art Museum), 1975 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 77)
  - Mullen, Buell, 1965; Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 78)
  - Museum of Modern Art, 1954-1964 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 79)
  - N - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 80)
  - Neugass, Ludwig, 1941-1944; Estate of, 1969, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 81)
  - Neumann, J. B., 1960 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 82)
  - P - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 83)
  - Perls, Hugo, 1968 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 84)
  - Picard, Lil, 1975-1978 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 85)
    Photos.
  - R - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 86)
  - Rebay, Hilla von, 1966-1969 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 87)
  - Rothko, Mark (Estate), 1975; 1978 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 88)
  - Rowland, David, 1965-1966 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 89)
  - S - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 90)
  - Schmitz, Ante, 1973-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 91)
  - Schultze, Bernard & Ursula, 1965-1973 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 92)
  - Seligman, Germain, 1962 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 93)
  - Sheeler, Charles, 1956 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 94)
  - Smith, W. Eugene, 1954 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 95)
  - Springer, Ferdinand, 1970 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 96)
  - Stavenhagen, Kurt, 1963 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 97)
  - Strauss-Ernst, Louise (Lou), 1941-1942 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 98)
  - Sweet, Ozzie, 1964 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 99)
  - Syz, Hans, 1966 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 100)
  - T - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 101)
  - Tages - Anzeiger, 1969-1974 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 102)
  - U - V - W - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 103)
  - Weinberg, Herman, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 104)
  - Wellensiek, Hertha, 1973-1977 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 105)
  - Weltkunst, 1971-1979 (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 106)
  - X - Y - Z - miscellaneous, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 107)
  - 65th birthday (1964), letters & clippings, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 108)
  - 70th birthday - clippings, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 109)
  - 75th birthday - clippings, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 110)
  - 80th birthday (1979) - cards & letters, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 111)
  - Condolence letters to Lotte Neugass, A - K, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 112)
  - Condolence letters to Lotte Neugass, L - Z, Undated (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 113)
  - Obituaries, 1979 June 16; Clippings. (Box 31 (13-Correspondence), Folder 114)
- Photographs by Fritz Neugass, 1950s-1979; 14; 164 file folders
  This series contains approximately 4500 original photographs and contact prints by Fritz Neugass. They are divided into two series: locations and subjects. Photographs include travel photographs of Greece and other Mediterranean countries, Cape Cod and Provincetown of the 1940s and 1950s, Mexico and the U.S. Southwest, and especially New York City. In addition, a number of the photographs have been reproduced and mounted, or have been reproduced in enlarged formats. This series also contains mounted photographs from two exhibits by Neugass: a Hypo-Hounds exhibit at the Users Club, NY, in the 1940s; and a Mexico Exhibit, shown at the American Museum of Natural History, NY, March 4-28, 1954.
  Arranged alphabetically, plus mounted photographs, oversized photos, and negatives.
  - Photographs, 14.1
    - American Midwest and Southwest, Undated (Box 32 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 1-2)
    - American Southwest, Undated (Box 32 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 3-8)
    - Berlin, 1955 (Box 32 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 9)
    - Boston, MA, Undated (Box 32 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 10)
    - Camp Catawba, Undated (Box 32 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 11)
    - Cape Cod - Nantucket - Auction, 1953 Summer (Box 33 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 1)
    - Contact prints, various subjects: Lake George (NY), Saratoga Springs (NY), Vermont, Albany (NY), New York City, Paris, Washington, D.C., Lake Champlain, Canada. 6. Cornwall, NY, Undated (Box 33 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 2-5)
    - Europe 1955: Berlin, Munich, Paris, Zurich, Undated (Box 33 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 7)
    - Florida, Undated (Box 33 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 8)
    - France - Italy, Undated (Box 33 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 9-10)
      Includes photographs of the Paris Exposition of 1937.
    - Garnet Lake, NY, Undated (Box 34 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 1)
    - Greece (1-6), Undated (Box 34 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 2-7)
    - Mediterranean: Turkey, Venice, Morocco, France, Italy (1-3), Undated (Box 34 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 8-10)
    - Mediterranean: Turkey, Venice, Morocco, France, Italy (4-8), Undated (Box 35 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 1-5)
    - Mexico: contact prints (1-3), Undated (Box 35 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 6-8)
    - Mexico (1-3), Undated (Box 35 (14-Photographs by Fritz Neugass), Folder 9-11)
      - A man and woman walking through the streets with..., ca. 1953
      - A quiet market scene with stalls and people..., ca. 1953
      - A boy leaning at a building corner, wearing a hat,..., ca. 1953
      - A night-time scene filled with candles and people..., ca. 1953
      - A baby wearing a striped shirt with holes waving...., ca. 1953
      - A small boy standing among donkeys in the stables...., ca. 1953
      - A girl carrying a baby on her back...., ca. 1953
      - A crowd of people at the market...., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - The American Museum of Natural History in 1954..., ca. 1953
      - A man and young man with sacks, wearing hats at..., ca. 1953
      - An old man in a black hat and glasses sits at a..., ca. 1953
      - A man and young boy wearing white shirts and hats..., ca. 1953
      - A woman draped in dark clothing, with her hair..., ca. 1953
      - A shore scene with a man working on a boat...., ca. 1953
      - Group of men in hats sitting on and squatting by a..., ca. 1953
      - A night-time scene filled with candles and people..., ca. 1953
      - Man in white shirt wearing a hat...., ca. 1953
      - A group of five women posing for a portrait with..., ca. 1953
      - The back of people kneeling and worshipping. The..., ca. 1953
      - Three young women with long skirts, black shawls,..., ca. 1953
      - Two women holding babies standing next to two men..., ca. 1953
      - A wedding scene with the bride and groom hooking..., ca. 1953
      - A man lying on a curb against a wall, with a..., ca. 1953
      - A young woman kneels while she irons clothes on..., ca. 1953
      - The back of two men walking with large baskets on..., ca. 1953
      - Two women, wrapped in shawls, sitting on the grass..., ca. 1953
      - A woman food-vendor selling tortillas...., ca. 1953
      - Four men wearing hats with large baskets on their..., ca. 1953
      - An old woman street-vendor sitting on the street...., ca. 1953
      - A shore scene with men tending to a boat with a..., ca. 1953
      - A crowded market scene, with lots of people, and a..., ca. 1953
      - Two young girls with wraps on their heads holding..., ca. 1953
      - A woman food-vendor selling tortillas with a baby..., ca. 1953
      - A man walking on an empty street, balancing a..., ca. 1953
      - A group of vendors, some sitting on large sacks...., ca. 1953
      - A market scene with people, baskets, and textiles...., ca. 1953
      - Boys in white shirts, carrying notebooks, gather..., ca. 1953
      - A young man dressed in Charro attire with a large..., ca. 1953
      - A woman with a baby in a sling on her chest...., ca. 1953
      - An old woman with some pottery...., ca. 1953
      - A market scene with a boy holding a basket on his..., ca. 1953
      - The back of a man with a backpack and hat, holding..., ca. 1953
      - A man with a hat squats against a wall while..., ca. 1953
      - A group of five men (some boys) standing by a pile..., ca. 1953
      - Woman with her eyes shut, sitting next to a basket..., ca. 1953
      - Group of men walking toward an arch way with cross..., ca. 1953
      - Boy standing in the shadow of a housing..., ca. 1953
        Conditions Governing Access
        Higher quality image available on request.
      - Woman holding basket at her waist, as the wind..., ca. 1953
      - Donkeys standing by a fence, with people on the..., ca. 1953
      - People sitting in the shade of an archway. A boy..., ca. 1953
      - A man wearing a hat, walking in the middle of two..., ca. 1953
      - A packed banquet hall scene of well dressed men..., ca. 1953
      - A large pile of clay pots stacked on the ground..., ca. 1953
      - An old woman standing with a boy and young woman...., ca. 1953
      - Two men in tunics and hats at a stall in San..., ca. 1953
      - Six men on the beach moving a long canoe toward..., ca. 1953
      - One woman sitting next to two older women, all in..., ca. 1953
      - Two men standing next to hats laid out and hung up..., ca. 1953